Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York Typographical Union No. 6 and NY Law Publishing Co., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- NLRB - NY Typographical Union No. 6 - Printing Industries of NY (Box 26, Folder 21)
- final Agreement - NY Typographical Union No. 6 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- contract - Printing Industry (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Correspondences and Memos - NY Typographical Union #6 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Prints Industries of Metro, NY Inc. and NY Typographical Union No 6, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Prints Industries of Metro, NY Inc. and NY Typographical Union No 6, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Printing Technology of NY, Inc. on behalf of Peter F. Mallon, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Prints Industries of Metro, NY Inc. (on behalf of Royal Composing Room, Inc.) Arnold Bauman), 1977 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Prints Industries of Metro, NY Inc. Joe D'Anna, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and Printers League Section, Prints Industries of Metro, NY Inc. (on behalf of Pandick Press, Inc.), 1977 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. On behalf of Skillset Typographers, Richard Marino, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of City Typographic Service Gabe Falsetta, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Typographic Designers, Inc. Robert Taylor, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Boro Typographers Norman Fallick, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Ad Press Ltd. George Marshall, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf on MJ Baumwell, Typography Emil Pscolka et al., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of boro Typographers, Inc. Norman Fallick, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Dispatch Press, Inc. Ronald Rease, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. Gerardo Reyes, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Haber Typographers, Arnold Friedman, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  May 8
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Song Printing Company Anthony Mancini, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Bowne and comp. Milton Morton, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of First Word, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. on behalf of Ad Press, Ltd., 1979 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Printers' League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc. and NY Typographical Union No. 6, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Publishers' Association of New York City, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  March 31, 1970 - March 30, 1973
- Publishers' association of NYC and NY Typographical Union No. 6, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Tri-Arts Press, Inc., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and tri-Arts Press, Inc. William Sisselman, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6 and Weltz Ad service, Inc. Murray Itkowitz, et al., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Printers League Section, New York/Employing Printers Ass., Inc., and NY Typographical Union No. 6, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Authorization Cars - Printing Industry (Box 26, Folder 56)
- Oil, chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Maritime Local 8-801, and Mobil Oil corp., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Maritime Local, 8-801 OCAW Int'l Union, and Mobile Oil Corp., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Petroleum Trades Employees Union, Inc. and gulf Oil corp. Edward P Leckey, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Typographical Union #2 (ITU) and Philadelphia Inquirer, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- PNWU, NY, and A&L Seamon, Inc., 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- PNWU, and AJ Siris Products Corp., 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- PNWU, and AJ Siris Products Corp Charles Gattridge, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- PNWU, and AJ siris Products Corp. McCoy Jennings, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- PNWA, NY, and AJ Siris Products Corp., 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- PNWU, NY and AJ Siris Products corp. Manuel Estrada, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- PNWU, NY, and AJ Siris Products Corp., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- PNWU, and Adam-Steven Leather Goods, Inc. Catherine Pesintz's, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- PNWU, and Adam Steven Leather Goods, Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- PNWU, and Adam-Steven Leatuer Goods, Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- PNWU and Alexander Wallets Corp. Luis Merger, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- PNWU, and Alice Handbag Co. John Brown, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- PNWU, and Allied Novelty corp. Ana Figueroa (Box 27, Folder 17)
- PNWU, and American Binder Comp. Alice Sangett, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- PNWU, and America Binder Company, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- PNWU, and APEX Leather Goods Manufacturing Company Robert Ottenberg, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- PNWU and Arrow Novelty company Helen Byrne, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- PNWU, and Art Craft Leather Goods L B Lewis, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- PNWU, and Art Leather Mfg., 1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- PNWU, and Astrid corp. Alexander Rosen, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- PNWU, and Bedford Mirror, Inc. Joe Santiago, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- PNWU, and Bedford Mirror, Inc., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- PNWU, and Berger Bros. Leather Goods co. Inc., 1965 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- PNWU and Block Handbag Eua Cargill, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- PNWU and Brightman Products, Inc. Amanda Cruz, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- PNWU, and Capitol Leather Novelty Mfg. Co. Edy Cortez, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- PNWU and CE Bon Handbags, Inc., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- PNWU and Celebrity, Inc. Ricardo Ruiz (Box 27, Folder 32)
- PNWU and Celebrity, Inc., 1969 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- PNWU, and Centra Leather goods Corp., 1955 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- PNWU and Centra Leather Goods Corp., 1956 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- PNWU Local 1 and Chelsea Towne Ltd., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- PNWU Local 1 and class Watch Strap co. Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- PNWU and Class Watch Strap co. Inc., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  Jan 14
- PNWU And Coblentz Bag co., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  April l5
- PNWU, and Colonial Novelties, Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- PNWU and Clearette Specialty Co. Carmen Aproyo, et al., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- PNWU and Concord Leather Goods Mfg. Co., 1971 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- PNWU and Crown Bag Craft co., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- PNWU and Craft Billfold Corp. Jose Velezquez, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- PNWU and Dandy Handbag Corp., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- PNWU and the Debway Corp., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- PNWU and the Debway Corp., 1965 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- PNWU Local 1 and Diamond & Sherman, Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- PNWU Local 1 and Diamond and Sherman Leather Goods, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Pocketbook workers Union of NY, and Dorset-Rex Products, Inc. Adolph Sternlieb, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Pocketbook workers Union of New York, Local No. 1 and Dorset - Rex Products Inc. Jack Tandeson, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- PNWU Excellent Bag Corp. Daniel Guzman, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- PNWU Local 1 and Excellent Bag Corp., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- PNWU Local 1 and Excellent Bag Corp., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- PNWU Local 1 and Fashion Princess Products Inc. (Princess Leather Goods), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- PNWU New York and Fayla Handbags Inc. Albert Riera, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- PNWU, Local 1 and Flair Handbag Inc., 1971 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- PNWU and Fleitman & Fleitman company angel Perez et al., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- PNWU Local 1 and Friedman Bros. Leatuer Goods, Inc., 1972 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union New York Local 1 and G and M Handbags, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 60)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, New York Local 1 and G and S Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, New York and Gail Leather Products, Inc. Elvira Florio, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union New York Local 1 and Gail Leather Products, Inc. James Oden, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' union New York Local 1 and Gail Leather Products, Inc. Victor Serrano, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 64)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union Inc. and Gail Manufacturing Co. Victor Delgado, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Pocketbook workers Union of New York and Gale Manufacturing, Inc. Benjamin Schuss, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY Local 1and Globe Handbag Inc., 1971 (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Pocketbook Workers Union, NY and Gold Seal Imports, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union and Guild Creations Inc., 1963 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York and Guild Creations, Inc., 1970 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, NY and Herz Specialty Products, Inc. Ann Staracio, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, NY and Hicraft Leather Products Corp., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Pocketbook and Novelty workers' Union, NY and Imperial Leather Goods co., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 73)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY and Klau Co. Inc., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, NY, Local (and Klau Associates, Inc.), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 75)
- PNWU NY and Knickerbocker Leather and Novelty co. Nathan Lifschitz, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 76)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY, Local and Le Soc Handbag Corp., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 77)
  Sept 19
- Pocketbook and Novelty workers' Union, NY and Lori Bags, Inc. Jack Friedman, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of NY and Majestic Loose Leaf co. Inc., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 79)
  Jan 18
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, NY and Mark Baren, Inc. Wilson Lopez, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 80)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union and Marnee Products, Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 81)
- Pocketbook and Novelty workers Union NY Local and Max Roth Leather Goods Mfg. Co., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 82)
- Pocketbook workers Union of NY and Mercury Leather Products, Inc., 1956 (Box 27, Folder 83)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, NY, Local 1 and Merzon Leather co., Inc. Julio Calabria, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 84)
- Pocketbook and Novelty workers' Union, NY, Local 1 and Milinari Original, Inc., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 85)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY and Millerond, Inc. Hermenio Torres, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 86)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY, Local 1 and Millerond, Inc., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 87)
- Pocketbook and Novelty workers' Union, NY, Local 1 and Mormac Co., Inc. Eleanor Neils, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 88)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of NY and NY Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Ronay, Inc., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 89)
- PNWU, and NY Industrial Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry, and Rocket Handbag, Inc., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 90)
- pocketbook workers' Union of NY and NY Industrial Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and signet Handbags Frank Epstein, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 91)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and the New York Industry Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry, and F & L Novelty company, Inc., 1955 (Box 27, Folder 92)
  Sept 5
- Pocketbook workers Union of NY and NY International Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Signet Handbags, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 93)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the NY Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, and Empress Handbag Comp., Inc., 1955 (Box 27, Folder 94)
- Pocketbook workers Union of NY and NY Industrial Council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Lovely Bags, Inc. Leoneia Hernandez, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 95)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry, and A Banner, Inc. Jack Klein, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 96)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc. Santos Live, Francisco Menendez, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 97)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc. Santos Live, Francisca Menendez, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 98)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 99)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and F. Milch, Inc., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 100)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Duchess Handbag Julio Bruno, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 101)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and F. Milch, Inc. Minnie Gottfried, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 102)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Pine Brothers, Inc. Samuel Silver, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 103)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of New York, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry and Lesco Limited, Inc., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 104)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, and continental Handbag, Inc. Virgilio Torres Lebran, et al. (Box 27, Folder 105)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Coblentz Bag Co. Hyman Catowitzky, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 106)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Handy Bag Co. Almo Domingo Ramos, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 107)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, and Dofan Handbag Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 108)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Ronay, Inc. Isidore Bruckner, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 109)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 110)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Mol-tone Bags, Inc. Eleanor Kehoe, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 111)
- Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union, NY and NY Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Harry Levine Corporation Ernesto Nieves, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 112)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry ad Etra, Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 113)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Irving Gaines, Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 114)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Edelman Bag Comp. (Helen-Beth Manf.) Isadore Kaminsky, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 115)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, and Egan-Wagner Merchandise corp. Carl Schwartz, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 116)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Garay and co., Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 117)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc. Hilda Karliner, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 118)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Magid Handbags, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 119)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, and Etienne Aigner, Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 120)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Glen Bags, Inc. Carmen Mana del Rodriguez, Juan Santana Castro, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 121)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Mondaine, Inc. Evelyn Hartman, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 122)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Coblentz Bagro Evelyn Nassar, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 123)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Lewis Purses, Inc. Juan Peraz, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 124)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Parisc Co., Inc. James Aquendo, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 125)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc., 1963 (Box 27, Folder 126)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc. Ethel Goodman, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 127)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Triangle Handbags Miguel Figueroa, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 128)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Egan-Wagner Merchandise Corp. Alice Van Lowe, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 129)
  Jan 8
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Excel Handbags co. Marie Seda Luz., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 130)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Lewis Purses, Inc. Henry Pearlman, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 131)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Dofan Handbag, Co., Inc. Joseph Springer, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 132)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Lowy and Mund Flossie Polk, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 133)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Garay and Co. David Eisenstaedt, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 134)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 135)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Pretty Bags, Inc. Hector Mendez, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 136)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Dobuler & Sons Leather Goods Corp. Herbert Flax., 1965 (Box 27, Folder 137)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial council of the National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry and Milch Handbags Hermenia Ortiz, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 138)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Lowy and Mund Beatrice Kissel, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 139)
  Nov 29
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and LaFrance Handbags, Inc. Morris Friedman, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 140)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Glen Bags, Inc., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 141)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags Helen Green, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 142)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 143)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Glen Bags, Inc. Felix Aponte, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 144)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags Doris Allen, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 145)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags Doris Allen, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 146)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and H and S Handbag Corp. Astley R. Clacher, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 147)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Glamor handbags, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 148)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Bellstone Handbags Dorothy Pickens, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 149)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Lucille Handbags, Inc. Alexander Fishman, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 150)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and smart Style Fashion Bags, Inc. Laurio Rosario, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 151)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 152)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 153)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Boris Handbags, Inc. Felix Laura, et al., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 154)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Pyramid Leather Goods co., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 155)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and John Romain, Inc., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 156)